#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sonalisethi-75b43452 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Apparel
Fashion Design
Sketching

### Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
Punjabi (Native or Bilingual)

# Sonali Sethi

Designer at Monte Carlo Fashions Ltd

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

# Summary

Experienced Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the apparel and fashion industry. Skilled in Trend Analysis, Fashion Illustration, Textiles, Apparel, and Adobe Illustrator. Strong arts and design professional graduated from National Institute of Fashion Technology.

# Experience

Monte Carlo Fashion Limited Design Manager April 2019 - Present

Monte Carlo Fashions Ltd Designer February 2015 - Present

#### NAHAR INDUSTRIAL ENTERPRISES LIMITED

Designer cum Merchandiser September 2013 - August 2014 (1 year)

Developed collections for International brands

## Education

National Institute of Fashion Technology Bachelor of Design · (2009 - 2013)

Sacred Heart Convent School, Ludhiana